http://usnrg.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
USEG:
Contact Us
Effective Date of Privacy Statement: February 18, 2008Last Updated: February 18, 2008.  In the most recent update, we updated our contact information which has been highlighted below.U.S. Energy Corp. appreciates your interest in this website. Your privacy is important and we want you to understand our practices with respect to gathering information from visitors to the Site and with respect to the uses we make of that information. Please check each portion or page of the Site that you visit. Certain portions or pages of the Site may contain changes to the Privacy Statement applicable to your use of that portion or page, for example, certain applications may request additional information from you.Information and UsesWhen someone visits the Site, our web servers automatically gather information that allows the site to communicate with the visitor’s computer during the visit. We also track such information as the number of visits to the site, which parts of the site visitors select, IP address (the Internet address assigned to your computer from your Internet Service Provider), domain type, browser type (i.e. Internet Explorer), date and time of day. We use those types of information for statistical purposes that help us design and administer the Site. Those types of information do not disclose Personal Information that would permit us to identify or locate individual visitors.Privacy concerns focus on Personal Information, that is, information that could identify a specific individual such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, and telephone numbers. If during your visit you personalize the Site, complete an order form, enter a contest, or submit other information to us, you may provide us with Personal Information. We may collect and use that Personal Information to provide you with products or services, to bill you for products and services you request, to market products and services which we think may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you for other purposes.As explained below in the section on Dissemination of Information to Third Parties, we do not distribute or sell Personal Information to third parties for the purpose of allowing them to market their products and services to you; moreover, as explained in the Opt Out/Modify Information section, we will make a reasonable effort to remove your Personal Information from our database in such a way that you will not receive future communications from us. If you notify us that Personal Information previously submitted to our site is no longer accurate, we will make a reasonable effort to make appropriate corrections.  To facilitate our efforts, it would be helpful if you could let us know the context in which you provided Personal Information, e.g in connection with promotion of a specific product or service.Information Placed on Your ComputerWe may store some information (commonly known as a “cookie”) on your computer when you look at or use the Site. This information facilitates customizing your use of the Site and ensures that you do not need to re-enter your details every time you visit it. You can erase or block this information from your computer if you want to. (Your ‘help’ screen or user manual should tell you how to do this.)Conditions of Use, Notices and RevisionsIf you choose to visit our Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our General Terms of Use, including any limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes and application of law provisions. We reserve the right to change this statement at any time without notice except as otherwise provided herein.Contacting U.S. Energy Corp.If you have any questions about the content of this Privacy Statement, please contact U.S. Energy Corp. at the following address:U.S. Energy Corp.4643 S. Ulster St.Suite 970Denver, CO 80237When we make material changes to this Privacy Statement, we will post the changes on this page and update the revision date at the top of the Privacy Statement.  We encourage you to visit our Privacy Statement regularly for updates.
675 Bering, Suite 100Houston, TX 77057  USA303-993-3200 • IR@USNRG.COM
.
© 2019 All rights reserved
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Legal Disclaimers
Powered by 2J2M, Inc.
